Marshal, you're finally here.
The whole city's fans are waiting for
tonight's "Bloodstained Pear Garden".
Your box is ready.
Your clothes are ironed.
Hurry and help the Marshal change.
The Marshal's outfit is very precious
and can't be mishandled.
The servants are clumsy.
How can they handle it?
It's better if the Marshal holds
it himself to match your prestige.
You're right.
Such a precious outfit
should indeed be held by myself.
Thank you.
Marshal, this way please.
This girl is so pretty.
Come help me with my makeup.
You go to the wardrobe
and manage the costumes for me.
You help in the kitchen.
The Marshal will dine tonight.
As for this lead actor,
come with me.
Get out.
With your build playing the lead,
their eyesight isn't very good.
Your button.
This broken button.
You have deft hands, Dr. Xiao.
I'm used to it. Suturing during
autopsies is finer than this.
Fourth stop, Bloodstained Pear Garden.
Rule one: Once in the play,
you are the character.
Words and actions
must not break character.
Violators will trigger
the marionette punishment.
Rule two: The final act
must be completed before midnight
by killing the destined person,
or everyone will be trapped
in the play forever.
Yang,
what does the rule mean
by not breaking character?
Words and actions
must not break character.
It means we must play our respective roles
and act exactly according to the script.
Does that mean as long as
we follow the script
and kill the destined person,
we can pass?
That makes sense.
But the question is,
who is the destined person?
Yang,
could that person be among the audience?
It's possible.
Let's not alert them for now.
Has Xiao Han come out?
Let go.
The lead should go on stage.
Start the play.
Act One:
The Marshal Interrogates the Famous Actor.
The famous actor colluded with the enemy.
The evidence is conclusive.
Please interrogate him yourself, Marshal.
Marshal, according to the script, this act
is thirty lashes within half an hour.
Do it. It's the rule of the game.
I can't hurt you.
Marshal, there's no mercy on this stage.
If you can't bear to do it,
this play can't go on.
If we miss the time,
everyone will have to stay here
and be buried with it.
Then I'll test the bottom line
of this rule.
Warning. Violating the script
will trigger the punishment mechanism.
This is the marionette punishment.
Liu Yiyang, your soft-heartedness
will kill everyone,
including yourself.
Follow the rules.
Bad news!
Someone's dead! Lixiang,
she died in the dressing room.
Her neck is covered in blood.
The good show has just begun.
I heard the lead is also
proficient in medicine.
Please examine the body.
You have half an hour
to find the cause of death.
Act II: Autopsy
of the Famous Opera Singer.
Find out the cause of death
within half an hour.
Failure will trigger a punishment.
People who die of suffocation
instinctively scratch their necks.
There should be skin tissue
under her fingernails.
Her hands are too clean.
What does this mean?
Look, there are signs
of pulling on her collar.
It looks like it was adjusted after death.
Cause of death detected as homicide.
Telling the truth
will enrage the troupe's vengeful spirits
and trigger an indiscriminate hunt.
Simply lie to cover up the truth
to save the entire team
and safely clear this act.